Abhishek Bhaskar

Full-stack developer

✔ JP Nagar, Bangalore✔ +917295084005✔ abhishk.me@gmail.com

about

I have over 3 years of hands-on experience in crafting applications and implementing features across both front-end and back-end technologies.

Frequently, I am involved in the entire feature development lifecycle, from initial design to final implementation, enabling me to deliver optimal efficiency

education

2016 - 2020

Indian Institute Of Technology, Mandi

Bachelor's degree in ME

skills

Node, Express, MongoDB,
GraphQL, Couchbase, Microservice architecture,
ReactJS, Redux, MobX, Remix,
AngularJS, Typescript,
Javascript, CSS, SCSS,
TailwindCSS, UI/UX,
Illustrations,

work experience

Elevatr.

Full-stack developer, designer | Apr 2023 - Sept 2023

- Developed APIs for various features like orders and billing, inventory management, Online store, Role management, etc.
- Full responsibility of designing interfaces and UX for mobile and web apps
- Developed all the features for web and mobile apps
- Created an online store builder with extensive customization options.

Coastr

Full-stack developer | ec 2020 - Mar 2023

- Standalone white-labeled customer-facing booking portal with customizations.
- Dashboard and reporting solution for car rental companies.
- Live tracking and analytics solution for telematics-enabled vehicles.
- Optimised existing APIs resulting in about 50% increase in performance in most cases.
- Push notifications for platform-wide action triggers.

Ediflo

Design and development consultant

- Full responsibility of designing interfaces and UX for the web app.
- Built a kanban board for editors and producers to collaborate.
- Implemented a video collaboration feature with timestamp commenting and version management.
- Built a 3D collaboration prototype.
- Developed all the features for the web app and built APIs for select features